The atmosphere is thinning out tonight
I'm drifting past the edge of the satellite
A velvet curtain falling on the glass
I watch the constellations slowly pass
Terminal velvet Painted in the black We crossed
the line And we can't go back Caught in the orbit
Losing the ground Floating away In the tide of
sound
Terminal Velvet
I'm telling the tree is quiet The screen is dark
Just a fading memory of the final spark.
The gravity is losing its heavy hold.
Out in beautiful,
silent cold.
Terminal valve is painted in black. We crossed
the line and we can't go back Caught in the orbit,
losing the ground Floating away in tidal sound
Terminal velvet
No friction to slow us down No gravity to pull us
to the ground Just the endless empty space A
perfect frozen state of grace
Terminal velvet Painted in the black We crossed
the line And we can't go back Caught in the orbit
Losing the ground Floating away In tidal sound
Terminal velvet.
Slowing away.